Guide to the Rose Goldsen papers, [ca. 1950-1985]
Goldsen, Rose papers, [ca. 1950-1985]
- Series VI Subject Files
  - Conceptual Subject Files
    - Evolution And Habitat
      - Bureaucracy creates a habitat. (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Social System, Culture And History
      - Property of a system versus characteristics of an individual (a necessary preface to understanding the concept of culture) (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - System and process - some examples of confusion betweewn micromotives and system (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Homo culturus - social circuitry (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Culture/system as process (circuitries) - MacLuhan, Watts, Bateson (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Sex is circuitry. Making love (human sex) is reciprocal noticing as well as mating. (Box 34, Folder 12)
        [File includes Legitimizing homosexuality. ]
      - Only if you understand that the social system is process, not mass, can you understand what it means t say Copernicus changed man's world; and those photographs showing our planet hurtling through space...? (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - What do you look at if you want to "see" the social system? Where do you look? Status, role, norms, rules- all are reciprocal; all are circuitries. (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - Expectations lie in social system: power-authority; status-role; norms-legitimacy; options-power. (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Concept of culture - Cultures can die as their relational systems are killed. (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - Cultures can die as their relational systems are knocked out. (Their loops are torn.) (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - Cultures can die as their relational systems are killed - examples. (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - History de-codifies. (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - History and time and cultural integrity (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - History, relativism, compromise (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - History is destroyed (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - The Production Model Op Man
      - Production model of man - fallen sparrow lecture (poetry, art, metaphor, etc.) (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - Production model of man; Morison on rights and responsibilities; genetics (Box 34, Folder 24)
      - When human eyes are replaced by electronic ones (Box 34, Folder 25)
      - TV news as culture power: perspective free perspective (Box 34, Folder 26)
      - Structure and function of mass media - clearing the air (Box 34, Folder 27)
      - RKG notes on automobile (Box 34, Folder 28)
      - Notes on Schumacherr Small Is Beautiful (Box 34, Folder 29)
      - Hidden costs in cost/benefit trade-offs (Box 34, Folder 30)
      - Property of system - academic tenure; PhD production (Box 34, Folder 31)
      - Spin of the social system - technological sex & Playboy (Box 34, Folder 32)
      - Work, work reforms (Box 34, Folder 33)
      - The production model exposed; alternative effects model- system effects rather than individual effects (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - EXPERIMENTS, SURVEYS, And Explanations
      - Explanation - relationships and process (Box 34, Folder 35)
      - Paradigm - the grammar of explanatory systems - example (Box 34, Folder 36)
      - In physics it is acceptable to replace mass by proces; as a paradigm for understanding matter. But social sciences are far behind. (Box 34, Folder 37)
      - One result is a whole experimental literature, which looks here, not there. (Box 34, Folder 38)
      - Stimulus-Response (S-R) Model - Skinner & Shockley: Goodbye autonomous man; hello autonomous environment (Box 34, Folder 39)
      - Sociobiology - biologizing violence, love, economics (Box 34, Folder 40)
      - Experimental method - incl Harlow's monkey experiment (Box 34, Folder 41)
      - Lecture 3 - Galileo's thought experiment; Galen; Copernicus (Box 34, Folder 42)
      - RKG notes on prediction, human freedom in social science (Box 34, Folder 43)
      - Experiments with human subjects (Box 34, Folder 44)
      - Electrical brain stimulation - RKG notes (Box 34, Folder 45)
      - Experts and expertise - engineering social system (Box 34, Folder 46)
      - Social indicators paradigm - data banks, census (Box 34, Folder 47)
      - Survey method - culture power (Box 34, Folder 48)
      - Polls and surveys - including on Vietnam (Box 34, Folder 49)
      - Polls, public attitudes re TV, ads - culture power (Box 34, Folder 50)
      - Media research, media paradigm (Box 34, Folder 51)
      - Statistical fallacy (Box 34, Folder 52)
      - Ad Hoc ism (Box 34, Folder 53)
    - LANGUAGE, COMMUNICATION, Noticing Structures
      - Animal behavior, senses, communication (Box 34, Folder 54)
      - Genesis of language - development in species (Box 34, Folder 55)
      - Acquisition of language - in chimps, gorillas (Box 34, Folder 56)
      - Acquisition of language - in humans, including retarded (Box 34, Folder 57)
      - Premack lecture - language and intelligence in ape & man 5/4/77 (Box 34, Folder 58)
      - Language - sociolinguistics, etc. (Box 34, Folder 59)
      - Language is habitat / Women and history (Box 34, Folder 60)
      - Organization of experience - Noticing structures lie in culture. (Box 34, Folder 61)
      - Language - noticing structure - gift, sex, linear grammar, smell (Box 34, Folder 62)
      - Noticing organs, language, time, myth (Box 34, Folder 63)
      - Time (Box 34, Folder 64)
      - On myth (Box 34, Folder 65)
      - Bibliography - Soc. 462, Spring 1978 (Box 34, Folder 66)
    - Child Development And Education
      - Child development paradigm (Box 34, Folder 67)
      - Autism - Tinbergen(s), et al (Box 34, Folder 68)
      - Educational paradigm, early socialization - Bateson, Alexander, education vs. schooling, etc. (Box 34, Folder 69)
      - Cross-cultural education paradigm (Box 34, Folder 70)
      - Cassette Special Communication System (CSCS) - education paradigm (Box 34, Folder 71)
    - Information, Opinion, Meaning, Creativity
      - ICODES Seminar - February 1975 (Box 34, Folder 72)
      - Information is power. When is information cashed?: Stone as type case. Also gov't information, privacy (Box 34, Folder 73)
      - Meaning resides in context (Box 34, Folder 74)
      - Media effects counter-paradigm - music, film, humor, etc. (Box 34, Folder 75)
      - Opinions as property - RKG memo 2/68; David Riesman reply (Box 34, Folder 76)
      - Vanishing point - An American Family, Carpenter -Mirror, Mirror; Raskin, etc. (Box 34, Folder 77)
      - Vanishing point - Watergate "effects," advertising (Box 34, Folder 78)
      - Vanishing point - art, music, science, creativity (Box 34, Folder 79)
      - Writers and artists: metaphor and creativity and groupthink (Box 34, Folder 80)
  - Miscellaneous Subject Files
    - New Communications Technologies And Networks
      - Cable TV (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Cable Bill and NFLCP comments (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Community television projects (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Computer networks; computerization of society (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Information Technology - Center for Urban Education (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Low Power Television (LPTV) (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - On-Line Media (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - The Report (Electronic Newsletter) (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Superstations - overview (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Satellite TV; videodisks, cassettes (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Warner-Amex/Qube - Two-way systems (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Videotex/Teletext (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Social Effects Of Communications Technologies
      - Democratic space readings (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Public/private notes, bibliography (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - [Social effects of communications technologies -notes/draft of manuscript?] - folder 1 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - [Social effects of communications technologies -notes/draft of manuscript?] - folder 2 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - [Social effects of communications technologies -notes/draft of manuscript?] - folder 3 (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - Social effects of communications technologies - RKG notes (Box 35, Folder 18)
      - New information society - RKG notes (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - Athens, Ohio [lecture?] - "Assessing the social impact of human communications systems" 4/84 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - Buffalo 11/22/82 - (Box 35, Folder 21)
        [lecture notes?]
      - John Berger/Abbe Moskowitz notebook (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - Privacy I and II notebooks (Box 35, Folder 23)
      - Privacy 3 and 4 notebooks (Box 35, Folder 24)
      - "Privacy and Democracy in 1984: A Humanistic View of New Communications Technology" - UCLA Law Program colloquia 12/10-12/81 (Box 35, Folder 25)
      - Stuart Brofman - Telecommunications 9/5/80 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - International Communications
      - International communications - unclassified (Box 35, Folder 27)
      - Development paradigm - advertising and the Third World (Box 35, Folder 28)
      - TV in Europe (Box 35, Folder 29)
      - TV and mass media in the Third World (Box 35, Folder 30)
      - International TV - Roy Colle articles (Box 35, Folder 31)
      - US government and international media; USIA; Voice of America (Box 35, Folder 32)
      - World Association for Christian Communication (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - News Programs And Documentaries
      - News shows and personnel; documentaries (Box 35, Folder 34)
      - Newsdoctors - Magid; McHugh and Hoffman, others (Box 35, Folder 35)
      - News and First Amendment (Box 35, Folder 36)
      - Notable Images - lecture 4/14/81 (Box 35, Folder 37)
      - "The Selling of the Pentagon" (CBS documentary) (Box 35, Folder 38)
      - "The Selling of the Pentagon" - leftovers, news clippings (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - White House Press Policy
      - Office of Telecommunications Policy (OTP) (Box 35, Folder 40)
      - Nixon, Agnew versus the Press (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - Public Broadcasting
      - Corporation for Public Broadcasting and CPB vs. PBS (Box 35, Folder 42)
      - CPB funding (Box 35, Folder 43)
      - Public TV/Educational TV 1966-70 (Box 35, Folder 44)
      - Public TV 1972-75 (Box 35, Folder 45)
      - Public broadcasting - 1974 funding bill (Box 35, Folder 46)
      - Lecture: Public TV (4/73) - folder 1 (Box 35, Folder 47)
      - Lecture: Public TV (4/73) - folder 2 (Box 35, Folder 48)
    - Broadcasting - Miscellaneous
      - Barnow [history of broadcasting] - RKG index (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Commercials (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Advertising - Soc. 252 lecture (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Index to commercials dubbed off Cindy's tapes (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - "You and the Commercial" (CBS) (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Fourth network (drop-ins) (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Larry Gross 10/2/81 - (Box 36, Folder 7)
        [lecture on TV and culture]
      - "The Impact of Mass Media Violence on US Homicides" -AAS prize-winning essay (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Liberation of the spectacle; TV environment is spectacle.. .anything! (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Matt McHugh, George Miller - House Committee on Family- correspondence 2-3/83 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Media codes (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Music Television (MTV) (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Nutrition and TV (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Political dissent (infiltrating media to discredit dissent) (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Polls: projecting election returns (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - Radio in the TV age; radio networks (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - Peggy Seal f on - videotaping (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - Sam Simon: Access - Cornell lecture (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - TV screen, physiological effects (Elizabeth Pienkos) (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - Social construction of reality - RKG lecture notes (Box 36, Folder 20)
      - Women, sex roles in the media (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Rkg Notes
      - Dr. Marjorie Burtt - RKG notes on therapy sessions (Box 36, Folder 22)
      - RKG - Howard Eaton correspondence re children's TV (Box 36, Folder 23)
      - RKG notes (Box 36, Folder 24)
      - RKG notes and comments (Box 36, Folder 25)
      - RKG notes - Roland Barthes, "Mythologies"; grammar of thought; book review notes, examples; examples of 2-pagers I like. (Box 36, Folder 26)
      - RKG notes - Bogota, March 1973 (Box 36, Folder 27)
      - RKG notes - May 1973 (Box 36, Folder 28)
      - RKG notes - miscellaneous (steno notebook) c. Fall IS (Box 36, Folder 29)
      - RKG notes - Richard O'Brien; breast-feeding; noticinc organs; experiments (Box 36, Folder 30)
      - The Bend of the River - notes (Box 36, Folder 31)
      - "Intellectual Journal" examples (Box 36, Folder 32)
      - Miscellaneous notes - creation myth, how to watch TV, predictability, etc. (Box 36, Folder 33)
      - Teilhard de Chardin - RKG notes (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Adoption, abortion (Box 36, Folder 35)
      - Aging (Box 36, Folder 36)
      - Agriculture - direct marketing (Pennsylvania Department of Agriculture) 2/76 (Box 36, Folder 37)
      - Agriculture - the Green Revolution (Box 36, Folder 38)
      - Architectural paradigm and urban planning - space as habitat (Box 36, Folder 39)
      - Urban planning paradigm (Box 36, Folder 40)
      - Neighborhoods (Box 36, Folder 41)
      - Cities as urban networks - lectures 4/14 & 4/16/75 (Box 36, Folder 42)
      - Welfare and poverty programs (Box 36, Folder 43)
      - Bibliography - satellites, communications policy (Box 36, Folder 44)
      - Bibliography - films, audio-visual (Box 36, Folder 45)
      - Bibliography - general texts (Box 36, Folder 46)
      - Bibliography - new technologies (Box 36, Folder 47)
      - Bibliography for "Communications Media in the Information Society" - The Washington School 1/27-3/17/82 (Box 36, Folder 48)
      - Bibliography -leftovers (Box 36, Folder 49)
      - Censorship - Ervin Committee hearings 3/72; David Rintels testimony (Box 36, Folder 50)
      - Censorship - Smothers Brothers 1969 (Box 36, Folder 51)
      - Censorship - unclassified (Box 36, Folder 52)
      - Credit and credit cards (Box 36, Folder 53)
      - Credit card controversy (Box 36, Folder 54)
      - Development paradigm (Box 36, Folder 55)
      - Development paradigm - "Policies for the Application Science and Technology to Development" (Box 36, Folder 56)
      - Ecological Disbalances (Shylock Syndrome) (Box 36, Folder 57)
      - Cayuga Lake controversy (nuclear power) (Box 36, Folder 58)
      - Economics paradigm (Box 36, Folder 59)
      - Family and Courtship (Box 36, Folder 60)
      - General Systems Theory - including Maruyama, Mumford etc. (Box 36, Folder 61)
      - Genetics (Box 36, Folder 62)
      - Experimental Genetics - Lederberg, Shockley, Goldsen 1966+ (Box 36, Folder 63)
      - Apt Illustrations, images, cartoons (Box 36, Folder 64)
      - Juvenile Justice - New York Times series (Box 36, Folder 65)
      - Soc. 205 readings - language (Box 36, Folder 66)
      - Lebow 10/5/83 - (Box 36, Folder 67)
        [lecture on military deterrence?]
      - Medical paradigm - unclassified (Box 36, Folder 68)
      - Biofeedback (seeks new medical uses for concept of ^ (Box 36, Folder 69)
      - Drugs and Medicines (Box 36, Folder 70)
      - Pharmaceutical paradigm - DBS, DMSO (Box 36, Folder 71)
      - Human transplants, psychosurgery, fetal research, implants, amniocentesis, cannibalism (Box 36, Folder 72)
      - Death (Box 36, Folder 73)
      - Mental Health Paradigm (Box 36, Folder 74)
      - The Name of the Rose (by Umberto Eco) - notes (Box 36, Folder 75)
      - Nicaragua Literacy Crusade (Box 36, Folder 76)
      - Play - Ed Devereaux, Rachel Carson (Box 36, Folder 77)
      - Population paradigm (Box 36, Folder 78)
      - Semiotics - notes, course outline (early version) (Box 36, Folder 79)
      - Sex, sex roles, discrimination against women (Box 36, Folder 80)
      - The social psychology of the gift (Box 36, Folder 81)
      - Sports paradigm (Box 36, Folder 82)
      - Yom Kippur - Sabbath rituals (Box 36, Folder 83)
      - To be filed (Box 36, Folder 84)
    - Public Interest And Pressure Groups
      - Accuracy in Media (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Committee for Open Media (COM), Phil Jacklin (Box 37, Folder 2)
        [PJ correspondence 4-5/73]
      - "Community Access TV" (newspaper) (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - The Network Project (Box 37, Folder 4)
        [Gregory Knox corresp 6-8/73]
      - Peoples Policy Center (Fred Harris) (Box 37, Folder 5)
        [Sherry Jones letter 8/73]
      - Priority One (Box 37, Folder 6)
        [Hal Carman letter 12/75]
      - Public Interest and Pressure Groups - unclassified (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Women's Institute for Freedom of the Press (Donna Allen) (Box 37, Folder 8)
        [WIFP Associate certificate 4/77]
    - Miscellaneous
      - AAAS Annual Meeting 1/82 (Box 37, Folder 9)
        [RKG notes 25pp]
      - ADTEL - test marketing (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Annenberg School Newsletter 1973-74 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - "Cable Copyright: Alternatives to the Compulsory License" (NTIA Report 12/81) (Box 37, Folder 12)
        [National Telecommunications and Information Administration]
      - Children and TV Violence (Box 37, Folder 13)
        [RKG notes 1p]
      - Children on Primetime Television - RKG notes (Box 37, Folder 14)
        [9pp]
      - Journal of Community Communications 1979-80 (4 issues) (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Local news (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Multichannel News 12/7/81 - RKG notes (Box 37, Folder 17)
        [7pp]
      - Ronald Frank and Marshall Greenberg, "Zooming in on TV Audiences" (Box 37, Folder 18)
      - "Organizing Notes" 1981-82 (3 issues) (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - Pastore Hearings (Senate Subcommittee on Communication 3/72; re: Surgeon General's Report on TV and Social Behavior (Box 37, Folder 20)
        [corresp 3-10/72]
      - Aftermath to Pastore Subcommittee Hearings 3/72 (Box 37, Folder 21)
        [John Murray corresp 8-10/72]
      - Pastore Subcommittee Hearings - miscellaneous 1971-73 (Box 37, Folder 22)
        [Nicholas Zapple letter 5/73]
      - "Pensions: The Broken Promise" (NBC documentary, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 23)
        [RKG notes 3pp]
      - Pornography 1/20/82 (Box 37, Folder 24)
      - Marcus Raskin; Institute for Policy Studies - Washington School brochure, Spring 1982 (Box 37, Folder 25)
        [Raskin, "The Writer in Modern Society" 10/81]
      - Repeats and Reruns (Box 37, Folder 26)
        [John Bass (FCC) letter 4/74; RKG radio script, "Repeats: The Six-Month Year"; notes 3pp]
      - Subliminal Advertising and Hidden Plugs (Box 37, Folder 27)
        [RKG notes 1]
      - Vanderbilt News Archives - mostly CBS Copyright Suit (1974) (Box 37, Folder 28)
      - Vanderbilt tapes - correspondence, phone conversations notes, radio program 3-12/74+ (Box 37, Folder 29)
        [radio program: "The Vanderbilt Tapes Revisited"; RKG notes 13pp; Ellen (Franklin) notes 9pp]
      - CBS vs. Vanderbilt - legal briefs c. 1974 (Box 37, Folder 30)
      - Video News 1979 (2 issues) (Box 37, Folder 31)
- Series VII. Photographs
  - RKG in canoe (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Colombia 1969 I - including RKG (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Colombia 1969 II (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Colombia 1969 III (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Colombia 1969 - contact prints (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Amazon - Leticia 1972 - Sheet 1, Envelope I (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Amazon - Leticia 1972 - Sheet 1, Envelope II (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Amazon - Leticia 1972 - Sheet 2 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Arara (Tikuna village) 1972? - I (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Arara (Tikuna village) 1972? - II (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Arara (Tikuna village) 1972? - III (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Bogota 1972 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Marco (Brazil) 1972 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Puerto Narino 1972 - Sheet 1 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Puerto Narino 1972 - Sheet 2, Envelope I - incl. RKG (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Puerto Narino 1972 - Sheet 2, Envelope II - incl. RKG (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Puerto Narino 1972 - Sheet 2, Envelope III (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Tarapaca - Villa Carmen 1972 - Sheet 1 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Tarapaca - Villa Carmen 1972 - Sheet 2 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Villalobos Family - to Tarapaca by boat, 1972 - I (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Villalobos Family - to Tarapaca by boat, 1972 - II (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Amazon c. 1972 or 1973 - including RKG (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Co tune 1973 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Puerto Narino - saw mill (Summer 1973, Roll 1) (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Leticia (and Puerto Narino?), including Mike Tsalickis (Summer 1973, Roll 1) (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Villa Carmen (Summer 1973, Roll 2) (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Summer 1973, Roll 3 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Saw mill - Puerto Narino (Summer 1973, Roll 3) (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Leticia (Summer 1973, Roll 4) (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Leticia - Dia de la Independencia, 7/20/73 - I (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Leticia - Dia de la Independencia, 7/20/73 - II (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Leticia - Dia de la Independencia, 7/20/73 - III (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Trip upriver - Amazon Queen - Summer 1973 - I (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Trip upriver - Amazon Queen - Summer 1973 - II (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Trip upriver - Amazon Queen - Summer 1973 - III -including Tikuna Children in Arara (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Trip upriver - Amazon Queen - Summer 1973 - IV -including Tikuna children in Arara (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - 3/75, Roll 1 - I (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - 3/75, Roll 1 - II (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - 3/75, Roll 1 - III (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - 3/75, Roll 1 - IV (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Melqar - 3/75, Roll 3 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Leticia - 3/75, Roll 4-1 (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - Leticia - 3/75, Roll 4 - II (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - Leticia - 3/75, Roll 4 - III (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - Leticia - 3/75, Roll 4 - IV (Box 38, Folder 45)
  - [Leticia] - including Mike Tsalickis wrestling snake (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - Street & market - Leticia; people at Leticia port-I (Box 38, Folder 47)
  - Street & market - Leticia; people at Leticia port-II (Box 38, Folder 48)
  - Idrobo (Box 38, Folder 49)
  - Arty shots - Amazon River and lagoons (Box 38, Folder 50)
  - Gabriela Samper (Amazon) - prints,, negatives, 2 slides (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Amazon - Leticia - 1972 - contact sheets, negatives (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Bogota; Marco (Brazil) - 1972 - contact sheets only (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Puerto Narino - 1972 - contact sheets, negatives (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Tarapaca, Villa Carmen - 1972 - contact sheets, negatives (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Villalobos Family - to Tarapaca by boat - 1972 -contact sheets, negatives (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Summer 1973 - contact sheets, negatives (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Cotuhe - 1973 - color negatives (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Leticia, Puerto Narino, Summer 1973 - Roll 1 - contact sheets, negatives (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Leticia, Puerto Narino, Villa Carmen, Summer 1973 Roll 2 - contact sheets, negatives (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Summer 1973 - Roll 3 - including Puerto Narino -contact sheets, negatives (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Leticia, Summer 1973 - Roll 4 - contact sheets, negatives (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Leticia - Dia de la Independencia (7/20/73) and tr upriver - Amazon Queen - color negatives (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - 3/75 - Roll 1 - contact sheets, negatives, large p (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Melqar - 3/75 - Roll 3 - contact sheets, negatives (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Leticia - 3/75 - Roll 4 - contact sheets, negative (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - [Commercial clothing, new puppies] 1975?; puppies 6/76 contact sheets, negatives, large prints (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Unidentified - including RKG - contact sheets, negatives (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Letter to RKG from Freddy Kienast (Cartagena 5/12/ - photos enclosed (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - "A Jungle Adventure - with all the comforts of home!" (brochure for the Hotel Parador Ticuna, Leticia) (Box 39, Folder 20)